trackmill.com 2015-04-07

# Trackmill - Home of The officially licensed Free Rider 2 Database

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on TrackMill or submit a level to one of our game databases.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to provide a valid e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site and experience its content anonymously without the need to register.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TrackMill. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their viewing habits online. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the appropriate Google pages regarding their ad and content network privacy policies. TrackMill does not handle or deal with these cookies directly.

Our other third-party advertisers may also use cookies, and have similar opt out options. Again, TrackMill does not directly dispense these cookies therefore we do not have direct access to allow users to opt-out.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
\- To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
\- To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our content based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other website feature.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your account. Your password is hashed and encrypted in our database and is NOT stored in real-text format.

**Intellectual Property & Content Ownership**

TrackMill features games and game construction utilities that are created either in-house by TrackMill or are licensed to us from third-party developers. These services are provided to visitors as-is.

Levels, tracks, puzzles, or any creation submitted to TrackMill via these construction utilities become the intellectual property of TrackMill and may be used in future releases without your consent.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences and login sessions for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third-parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the practices of domestic and international laws, enforce our specific website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety from potential harm.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel on the forums and going to the "User CP" page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens' Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 7 July, 2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
privacy@trackmill.com
